Curriculum Vitae

My name is Samuele.

I'm an Italian spatial data scientist passionate about GIS & programming. Currently, I work at Eurac Research providing scientific consultancy to public authorities.

The best way to get a hold of me is via email: samuelezilio95@gmail.com. You can also find me on GitHub: https://github.com/samuzilio.

Work Experience

06/2024 - Ongoing

Researcher

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

05/2021 - 05/2024

Junior Researcher

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

09/2020 - 04/2021

Trainee

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

Education

2017 - 2020

MSc in Urban and Regional Planning

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + Universidade de Lisboa, Lisbon (Portugal)

2014 - 2017

BSc in Urban and Regional Planning

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + İstanbul Teknik Üniversitesi, Istanbul (Turkey)